Is it like what you imagined?
It's different.
This should be my
first time on Heart Signal Watch Party.
I'm a little bit curious,
and also a bit
excited.
Look, there's a board over there.
Every guest on Heart Signal Watch Party
takes a group photo
and puts it there.
Then ours should be
this season's
first group photo.
So happy.
Let's sit down first.
Have a seat.
I'm a bit excited to see
who the other guests are today.
Hello.
Long time no see.
The last time we met was probably
during the sports meet.
Yes.
Welcome.
Glad to have you here.
Have a seat.
So, are we going to
start eating now?
Then,
let's introduce ourselves first.
Even though we're old friends.
Hello, everyone.
I'm from the Ruyi Couple,
Xu Rulan.
It's my turn.
Right, it's your turn.
Hello, everyone. I'm from the Ruyi Couple,
Fang Yijiong.
Is it Dr. Fang's first time here?
Yes, this should be my
first Heart Signal Watch Party.
This time it just happened to work.
Right, our schedules aligned.
Are you nervous?
It'd be a lie to say I'm not nervous,
but I'm okay
since Lanlan is here with me.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Zeng Zhaohao's fiancée,
Zhang Jin.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Zhang Jin's fiancé,
Zeng Zhaohao.
You two are already fiancé and fiancée.
Do you have any future plans?
Our near-term plan is to get our marriage license.
Because as for the wedding,
we just realized
it's a lot of work, right?
Yeah.
Like booking the Big Four.
They're very hard to book.
I mean,
the popular and good ones
are fully booked.
Yeah.
Including where to choose the venue.
Anyway, it's a really
huge project.
So right now,
you still feel like you're madly in love,
right?
Yes.
But I do have a slightly
different feeling.
Like, when you're just dating,
in the early stages, it might be
more about
the two of you together
enjoying life
and having some fun.
But the moment my status changed,
I suddenly felt that
I really need to take on more
responsibilities and duties.
For me,
I have this
self-driven
sense of responsibility.
"Brainwashing."
That's great, Babe.
I need to work hard too.
I'll work hard too.
So do you two feel
like anything has changed?
This past year has been pretty good.
Yeah.
It's had its ups and downs.
But most of the time,
we're very happy.
However, there are
a lot of outside voices.
So we've basically
been through a lot together.
And after adapting to each other,
we understand each other better.
Emotionally, it also
just gets stronger and stronger.
There are arguments,
but after we argue,
we actually
understand each other more.
Right.
Yeah, I feel that too.
Like, when both sides have
different opinions,
it's actually a way
to communicate our feelings.
It lets the other person know
where your boundaries are.
Yeah.
There's bound to be an adjustment period.
As long as
you repair the relationship afterwards,
I think it'll be fine...
Right.
I think it's something every couple
has to go through.
Exactly.
So how are things between you now?
The sense of ritual in our daily lives
actually still
remains the same as before.
We just celebrated our one-year anniversary.
I saw that video,
the one with Dr. Fang lying on the floor
being dragged away.
Yeah.
It was staged.
He dragged me into filming
that random one.
And then it was my birthday.
Let's put the crown on Lanlan first.
I want to wish you...
Sometimes your health is really poor,
so you need to sleep on time.
And I hope you get healthier,
and can fall asleep every night.
So,
we're also playing a little game today.
And the winning couple
will get
a set of Heart Signal merch.
The losers have to do
a silly,
four-panel meme photoshoot.
This game is called
the couples' version of
"I Have, You Haven't."
We'll go first.
Okay.
Then you start.
I'll do the first one.
Okay.
Let's quickly think of something.
It's fine, let's hear
how far they'll go first.
We had crayfish yesterday.
"Uh-oh."
Let's put a finger down then.
I have a "trump card."
Let's hear it then.
Congratulations!
You go first.
I know.
We just celebrated our one-year anniversary.
That's nothing.
We've celebrated a one-year anniversary too.
Just recently.
We just celebrated our three-year anniversary.
Well, we just celebrated our one-year anniversary this past month.
Put a finger down.
Think of one, Babe.
I got one.
We have a puppy.
Oh no.
Next.
Our turn.
We are right now...
holding hands.
Holding hands.
Half a beat late.
Put a finger down.
Let me think.
Brain working at full speed.
Think fast.
I am. I'm thinking.
My brain is only one kilobyte.
Yours probably has a bit more capacity than mine.
I thought of one.
Zhang Jin has drank with my dad.
Well...
Not bad.
"Bet" correctly.
Nice.
Our turn again.
We need to take a four-shot sequence.
You name one.
Let me think.
The two of us...
first met on an island.
"Uh-oh."
We put another finger down.
Then we're "doomed."
We only have one left now.
What do we do?
We've both appeared on
Heart Signal's
Heart Signal Watch Party.
Let me think.
We're both nearsighted.
Well, the thing is...
you really can't put a finger down for that.
You really can't.
We both are too.
Are you two as well?
So you're all nearsighted.
Do you know how high the rate
of nearsightedness is nowadays?
Then we lose.
We lose.
Then our winners
can claim
our prize.
This is pretty. Baby blue.
Thank you.
Later, when we're done filming,
I'll pack up the
fruits and stuff on this table
and take them with me.
Take them with you.
Like stuffing them in your pockets, right?
Right.
Pack them up and go.
Come on.
A goofy four-shot sequence.
Then I need to stand up.
Yeah, shouldn't you get in the back?
Sure.
Here we go, second shot.
We need to widen our eyes.
You need to widen your eyes.
Again.
One more.
They're so sweet.
This isn't goofy at all!
Yeah.
This is a reward.
Alright, now we've
arrived at our most anticipated
video-watching segment.
So excited.
A beat too late.
Alright, let's begin.
Super excited.
I'm more nervous than all of you right now.
So pretty.
This sounds hilarious already.
When will we get a Northeast season?
They all seem to be
very direct.
They're all so pretty.
I feel like the word "brave"
has appeared in their
introductions many times.
"Bold and proactive."
These words are already
very straightforward.
I guess they will also
each choose a type,
just one card.
I like them all.
So this is about picking
the kind of love you long for,
right?
Yes.
Sincere.
That's great. This description,
this description is so good.
Come on, let's make a wish together, the four of us.
I will always...
I want to invite you into the future I've planned.
Will you be my girlfriend?
I'm really looking forward to entering
the next stage with you in a new role.
Are you willing to let Ponyo take care of Abi more,
and let me take care of you more?
I am.
Yes.
Babe, you're the right one for me,
right?
Okay, earlier, each guest actually
got four cards.
If it were you guys,
which space would you choose?
I'd choose the biggest space.
I'd choose the 180-square-meter one.
Xiaobao is so funny.
Let me see.
Passionate and energetic love.
Independent and autonomous love.
Empathetic and companionable love.
They all feel really right.
It's so hard to choose.
True.
You chose this one.
Right.
Not this one.
I wouldn't choose this one either.
I hope two people can
do things together and keep each other company. So...
Plus, couples should stick together.
I really don't want to choose this one.
Okay, then let's choose this one.
Choose this one.
Then it seems the four of us
made the same choice.
You all chose my lucky color.
Why are you looking forward to
a love of shared frequency and understanding?
I suddenly thought of a slightly cheesy saying,
which is,
falling in love is easy,
but staying in love is to be cherished.
I think if you,
if two people can stay in love,
it will require
mutual understanding and tolerance.
You'll be on the same frequency in many ways,
and move forward together.
Right, when the friction and resistance of being together
aren't that high,
you'll keep loving each other forever.
Yes.
That saying is a bit cheesy.
Sorry about that.
You have to understand a thirty-year-old.
What about yours?
Because I feel that
in an intimate relationship,
both people will be
to each other
the person in this world
they are closest to.
Actually, everyone has emotional ups and downs.
When you're feeling down,
you hope someone can catch some of
your negative emotions.
And when something really happy
happens to you,
you will also
hope someone can share that happiness with you,
and genuinely applaud you.
Yes.
So I think
this, to me,
is actually very important in a relationship.
I think in daily life,
the moments that best show our connection...
Actually, I think it's just
not having to speak.
For example, if two people
are deciding where to eat today.
Right.
Just say, "Let's go."
Yeah.
Right?
Same goes for traveling.
Just packing up and leaving.
If you're not happy today,
I can tell at first glance.
You...
sometimes you've already said
you don't want to talk to me today.
Then I'll just step aside and
wait a bit.
Just step aside and wait a bit.
But I don't really say,
"I don't want to talk to you."
I still want to talk
to you.
Let's keep watching.
Okay.
Cui Kaiyi.
She seems a bit nervous.
Going in first...
The wait is the most...
When you went in,
were you the first?
Yes.
There was no one when I went in.
But I wasn't nervous.
I thought it was exciting.
Yeah.
Everyone feels differently.
Someone's here.
Here they come.
Companionship.
That's the one we just
chose.
The blue one (empathic companionship).
Then he and that girl
probably won't end up in the same room.
Right, exactly.
What's this? Where are they going?
Are they coming back for dinner?
Zhao Xilun.
Sha Yue'er.
What a pretty name.
Their outfits match well, too.
They haven't even entered the house,
and they're already introducing themselves.
Are they going back?
Or just chatting here?
Plus, they actually picked
different colors initially.
How come they left together?
The guy is thinking,
"Why did I choose this one?"
Then he just switches right there.
It's okay.
If they're The right one, they'll meet again.
Intertwined.
So they have four rooms.
You just realized?
Weren't there four cards?
No, I'm thinking...
could it be that someone will just
sit there from start to finish?
There might be
a very unevenly distributed
kind of
situation.
It's possible.
They both chose
to sit on the same sofa
I didn't sit
next to you back then.
Right.
Yeah.
You didn't choose to sit next to me.
Why?
I felt that sitting side by side
wasn't great
for talking.
We should sit face-to-face.
Right?
Kind of like me and Zeng,
at this angle.
Maybe a bit further over.
So you can observe,
and interact at the same time.
Right.
So back then,
I actually put thought into it,
okay?
Right.
If it were your first time meeting,
and it was you two guys meeting,
how would you break the ice?
Hi.
I'm dying laughing.
Do I not have an accent?
I don't have an accent.
This girl has such a great personality.
They're having a great chat.
They immediately
hit it off.
Yeah.
When they compliment each other,
they don't look into each other's eyes.
They look straight ahead.
They're too shy to do it directly.
This fits perfectly with
the type to choose a safe commitment.
The way they describe things
puts the other person
in a quite comfortable state.
That's the vibe.
Look.
Striking features.
So for you two,
in your daily life, do you still,
like, often
compliment each other like them?
We do.
How do you usually
compliment each other?
I just straight up compliment him.
Just go full-on with him.
Give him full emotional support.
What about you guys?
We do it too, actually.
Like on my birthday,
I just said,
"You look handsome today."
And at that moment,
he didn't catch it on video.
He told me to say it again.
Later, I found out
he actually did catch it.
He just wanted to
hear me say it again.
Dr. Fang is being sneaky.
Let's keep watching then.
Okay.
Cui Yihang.
As soon as he sat down,
he thought of getting her water.
Very thoughtful.
I feel like
I'm seeing myself in him.
Awkward?
Yeah, in this guy.
"Little Bodyguard."
Dry humor.
Very dry. Have some water.
But I think he's actually
a very confident person.
When he speaks,
he always
looks into the girl's eyes.
Very sincere.
In this kind of new environment,
everyone gets a little nervous.
It's normal.
Here comes another one.
He's very relaxed.
Yeah, a cheerful guy.
He seems to be sitting
where Dr. Fang
used to sit.
Yeah, exactly.
Right.
They are all trying so hard not to laugh.
I feel like their
vibe this season
is very different
from our season.
Really?
Compared to them,
we seem much more reserved.
They're so direct.
Their words all have this
dominant feel.
Right.
He took the fall for her.
It's like when...
it's like in an elevator,
your boss farts,
and you raise your hand
and say, "That was me."
That's so funny.
I'm not leaving.
I'm watching this to the very end.
Once I finish watching,
I want to
put their names
together! Actually, I already did!
You see, this guy is
a very confident person.
He actually follows up and asks her.
Babe, you're amazing.
Super amazing.
Look, I complimented you.
Complimenting her directly.
"I really am amazing."
You really dare to speak up.
One dares to ask, the other to answer.
This blue one
has no one in it.
He looks so awkward.
He's
nervously picking at his card.
Someone's coming.
I bet it's a guy.
A girl.
A guy is here.
Two guys.
Reward me with a piece of watermelon.
Here.
Here, your reward.
What if this blue one
ends up
with only two guys?
What's gonna happen then?
They'll just develop
a very deep Bromance.
How did they get to talking about gaining weight?
They're forcing the conversation.
Bringing up every random topic possible.
Their conversation is so awkward.
I feel like none of these topics can go anywhere.
And the hand rubbing.
Come on, let's rub our hands together.
Come on.
I think the two of them
already have a "Bromance".
I think so too.
There really isn't.
There is, smell it.
I don't want to smell you.
So random.
"I can't."
It's a bit random.
Are they going to
keep doing this?
They're hilarious.
What if you're actually right,
and it's just them in the end
in this
blue (empathetic love)
room?
It's possible.
Someone's here.
A guy or a girl?
But it seems that
yellow (secure commitment)
is chosen by more girls.
Yeah.
The yellow (secure commitment) room
has a lot of people too.
There's no one yet
choosing green (independent love).
Here comes one.
The first one to choose
green (independent love) is a guy.
The sky is gradually getting dark.
He's starting to realize something's wrong.
You just stay independent here,
all by yourself until the end.
Will he regret
picking this card?
If it were you guys,
would you feel
extremely tormented,
and not know what to do?
I would.
Like, you'd feel you might have
actually been "eliminated."
Because no one comes to notify you.
You're forgotten.
Someone's here.
Here they come.
The girl just now was just passing by.
Keep waiting.
Actually, I think he
is under a lot of pressure.
Being there all alone
for so long.
Would you break down if it were you?
I wouldn't say break down,
but I'd probably be a little shaken.
I'd wonder if everyone else is already
having great conversations.
Does it feel like
you're a bit
left behind?
Yeah, a bit.
He will "break out."
I think he will "break out."
The two of them even switched seats.
Yeah.
They really are
"Her bodyguards."
That's a very detailed observation.
They didn't let
the girl choose.
Right.
Why didn't the two of them
talk about this earlier?
Why did they talk about "chicken poop" before?
Talking to a girl about "chicken poop"...
is just too random.
Actually, once a girl joins in,
the whole vibe
is completely different.
Yeah.
Like, in front of your bros
versus in front of
the girl you like,
would your behavior
change a lot?
Tell us more.
Actually, I think
what the two of them
were chatting about just now
was pretty obvious.
At first, their topic was
smelling "chicken poop".
But...
after the girl came in,
their topic became
"I like road trips."
The conversation turned into
"I want to attract you,"
"I want to show off,"
showing their independent side.
Right.
Let's keep watching.
Okay.
They've all arrived.
This season,
it's pretty innovative.
They're not in the same room,
but they can use the screens
to see the other rooms
and what's happening.
They can even swap.
Swap colors.
The guy in the shirt (Zhao Xilun)
is definitely going to find
that girl in red (Sha Yue'er).
Not necessarily.
I think he will.
I think so too.
Green (independent love)
Will he leave?
He probably will.
He's so happy.
Let me tell you,
he will definitely go.
He really swapped!
See?
As expected.
See, we were right.
As expected, women's intuition
is very accurate.
I'm wondering if he
might be
afraid of being too direct,
and she wouldn't accept it.
So he didn't say it.
He said he wants to see everyone.
What he just said
was actually
a very safe statement.
Because this way,
the other person won't feel particularly
awkward.
So subtle.
I think it's very subtle too.
You know?
It's hard to describe.
If
guys talk in front of you
about video games,
does it affect your impression of them?
Then I'd just think
the time he could spend with me,
he spends playing games.
I'd be a little worried.
I'm afraid he'd just play games all the time.
Right.
On your phone,
those mini-games...
what are you playing?
Zhao Yun and that...
You play that too?
Just recently.
He also played that...
the one where you deploy minions.
Right.
A tower defense game.
"I can't."
We're out of here.
You two have fun.
We'll play together from now on.
We'll play dress-up games.
Let's keep watching.
Okay.
Are we voting already?
If I haven't seen them,
for my first vote,
it'd be hard to choose
someone I haven't seen.
I think so too.
So you'd definitely choose
someone you've seen.
I'd choose someone I've seen.
Anchoring effect.
That's also a kind of destiny.
Actually,
yeah.
We picked each other.
So we picked each other back then.
Why else would they say
it's destiny?
I'm really curious
who will get the most votes
among the guys and girls.
I think it should be Sha Yue'er.
And for the guys, it should be
Sun Bohan.
Because I feel like
in that room,
there are more guys.
And in that room,
there are more girls.
I think your logic is right.
Since we just talked about how
people generally wouldn't choose
someone they haven't met.
Right.
You're so smart.
You're using logical deduction.
Zhang Haoyun actually has logic!
You're so smart.
I agree.
We're on the same page.
We both think that
Sha Yue'er will be the most voted girl.
And for the guys, it should be Sun Bohan.
I think
the most popular girl
might be Cui Kaiyi.
Cui Kaiyi.
Right, Cui Kaiyi's personality
is very outgoing.
People who are very outgoing on the first meeting
are easily noticed by everyone.
Right, when she interacts with the guys,
she's really good at giving emotional support.
Anchoring effect.
Among the guys, it might be
Chen Hewen.
The guy might be Chen Hewen.
Then whoever loses
buys the winner a big meal.
Sounds good.
Deal.
So, after watching this part,
what are your thoughts?
I feel like everyone should just
be
their most authentic
and sincere selves.
And then you'll meet another
sincere soul.
Then you'll spark a connection,
and it'll be just like this,
bursting into
sweet, sweet love.
I wish that Heart Signal Season 9's
guests
can all find
someone who makes their heart
flutter.
And then experience
a beautiful love.
If you like someone, go for it!
Yes!
Don't leave yourself
with any regrets.
Okay.
Come on.
Okay, now let's
take a group photo.
Okay!
Heart Signal Watch Party!
The heartbeat goes on!